P.O.Box 05, Nungua Accra, Greater Accra GZ-095-3565, Ghana Cell: +233 555272696 dennisbortey60@gmail.com

[System Admin] / [Web Dev] / [App Dev]

Profile

I am a certified Systems and Networking Engineer, specialized Web and Mobile App Developer. Expert in Graphic Design as well. Graduated from Intercom Programming And Manufacturing Co. (IPMC) Ghana, Professional Diploma in A+,N+,Linux Administration, experienced systems manager at Studio U Ghana, General Science student with a WASSCE certificate. Self thaught computer scientist with intermediate level of experience. I am a very fast learner and good communicator in what I do as an IT specialist.

Accomplishments

- Coded HTML and drafted design documentation to aid future code usage and modification.
- · Customized networking system for easy addressing and assigning of clients and users
- Solution expert in Infrastrucure Microsoft
- Volunteer in graphic design EarnestWrites
- [Another accomplishment, achievement, award or promotion.]

Experience

Studio U, Osu, Accra

Systems Manager, 12/2019 - 3/2021

Performed hardware and software support and installation. Managed support system engineers performing on-site customer service and maintenance. Performed weekly back up of energy management data. Operated computer help desk assisting users with problems and solutions. Experienced with computer hardware including personal computers, servers, and mainframe clusters. Established a corporate standard desktop. Skilled at diagnosing and repairing personal computers.

- Skilled at diagnosing and repairing personal computers
- Experienced with computer hardware including personal computers, servers, and mainframe clusters
- Provided technical support to Managers on software and hardware issues

Earnest Writes, Remote, Ghana

Graphic Design, 1/2022 - 4/2022

Graphic design for flyers, Ads, Books and Banners

- New design patterns to blend brand design with mordern designs
- Submission of tasks before deadlines
- · Gained access to more tools and apps

Education

H.S. Diploma, [Major], 9/2019

Intercom Programming and Manufacturing Co. Gh, Spintex, Accra GPA: 2.65

Advanced courses in A+,N+,Linux,Windows Server,Linux Administration,Cloud computing.

Skills

- Problem Solving
- Project Management
- System Administration
- Computer/Network Security
- Configuration Management
- Cross-Functional Technology Team
- Client Needs Assessment
- Computer/Network Security
- End-User Training
- Graphic Design
- Interface Design
- IT/Web Content
- Application Development
- JavaScript

Affiliations

Systems Engineers , 9/2018 - 9/2019 IPMC-Systems Engineers , Spintex,Accra

IT mangaement, 12/2019 - 3/2021 Studio-U, Osu

Licenses

System Engineering, 9/2018 - 9/2019 IPMC

Microsoft Partner, 9/2018 - 9/2019 Microsoft-IPMC

Graphic Designer, 1/2022 - 4/2022 Earnest Writes

Training

Programming, 1/2019 - 7/2019 DeVslopes, Remote

Honors

A+ and N+, 9/2018 - 9/2019 IPMC *Graphic designer*, 1/2022 - 4/2022 Earnest Writes

Talent

Graphic Designer *media and design* Carli Buckle

Volunteer

Carli Buckle, Kumasi, Ghana

Graphic Designer, 1/2022 - 4/2022

Instructed and trained agency staff and volunteeres in skills required to provide services. Assigned duties to staff and volunteered.